{
   "questions":[
      {
         "question": "Do you often _____________ your granny?",
         "answers": [
            "call",
            "calls",
            "calling",
            "called"
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "call"
      },
      {
         "question": "What are they doing now in the garden? I think they _____________ the plants.",
         "answers": [
            "is watering",
            "are watering",
            "watered",
            "waters"
            
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "are watering"
      },
      {
         "question": " Laura is busy at the moment. She _____________ her students’ homework.",
         "answers": [
            "checks",
            "are checking",
            "is checking",
            "checked",
            "check"
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "is checking"
      },
      {
         "question": "Maria Sharapova, a famous tennis player, _____________ the first Russian woman athlete who won Wimbledon.",
         "answers": [
            "becomes",
            "was become",
            "has became",
            "became",
            "will become"
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "became"
      },
      {
         "question": "Did you _____________ it?",
         "answers": [
            "did",
            "does",
            "was doing",
            "done",
            "do"
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "do"
      },
      {
         "question": "It’s very dangerous to go out alone at night so you must take care of _____________.",
         "answers": [
            "you",
            "myself",
            "themselves",
            "yourself"
            
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "yourself"
      },
      {
         "question": "Please fill _____________ this registration form to get a membership of our swimming pool.",
         "answers": [
            "up",
            "out",
            "with",
            "in"
            
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "in"
      },
      {
         "question": "The young boy _____________ house was burnt is weeping.",
         "answers": [
            "whose",
            "who",
            "which",
            "that",
            "whom"
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "whose"
      },
      {
         "question": "_____________ the door be closed.",
         "answers": [
            "was",
            "is",
            "let",
            "will",
            "are"
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "let"
      },
      {
         "question": " I work _____________ 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. on Mondays.",
         "answers": [
            "to",
            "from",
            "in",
            "till",
            "on"
         ],
         "rightAnswer": "from"
      }
   ]
}